<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | SEGMAC]]></title>
  <link href="http://duanhong169.github.com/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://duanhong169.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-04-19T18:20:52+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://duanhong169.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[弘]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The social life in my mind]]></title>
    <link href="http://duanhong169.github.com/blog/the-social-life-in-my-mind.html"/>
    <updated>2012-04-04T21:28:44+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://duanhong169.github.com/blog/the-social-life-in-my-mind</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Every human can't live out of the social, and so we build a very big social around the world, and then we live in it,  we help each other, build our own land, so us human beings become stronger and stronger--we become the kings of the world.</p>

<pre><code> As a human, we must be a part of the social or we'll be cancelled...It's no doubt we'll be cancelled if we don't do something to adapt to the social life, the social nature. 
 You must want to know what is life and what is social life.well, sometimes we say life, this life most means our individual life. But truth be told, our life has two part--the social life and the individual life.
 Every morning we get up and open our eyes, it's our life,our individual life. we can't deny that social life is more difficult than individual life, we meet many different people and many different affairs, many problem for us to solve. As it is more difficult, some people want to run away from it. If a man run away from the social life, there is only one result, he'll fail, he'll never make any progress, and at last, he dead with nobody else feel sad...like he never come to the world. 
 Strictly speaking, human is a type of animal that tends to lead a social rather than individual life. If you like, it’s easy to collect a bulk of strong and indubitable evidences to defend this. But isn’t true? What kind of social life the word covers? Beyond boundary of common sense, the word “social”, herein, not only embraces some things as bait fame and accumulate property by all means, not narrowly peer at all gathering in a mess in the street or grand hall. But, in my limited perspective, also emphasizes on one of main bridge which span the gap between countries, races, color, even languages: right reasoning. 
  However, in our current society, a common picture becomes more difficult to draw in our hand.  Much time we wasted on one-eyed monster (TV, and new digital gadgets), around the corner of cyber web, etc. Solitude is like a haunting ghost we scare to be in face with. If not, where to get clear reason and make right decision on short-term, and long-term demand? 
 If you want to be one part of the social life,first,you must know how to learn something aboat other people,whenever I meet new people, I’m always curious to find out where they’re coming from so I can better understand who they are. This is natural, I know. The only difference is that to me, this means finding out about their past relationships. Strange, right? I’ve concluded that this is because I define myself by my relationships and therefore apply the same rules when trying to learn about other people.Well, it's just my way, and every body has their own ways.No matter which way you do, the most important thing is that you should know the man you want to do thing with.
 But what I say is just say, you must do it, we say practise is the best teacher, and so it's right here, we must take part in the social life and practise time afer time, then I believe every body has ability to handle it well.
 Now we're college students, as soon as we graduate, we will really become one part of the social, and it's time for us to show our skills, our ability, our advantages and so on. We must show our best to the other so we can be accept by others and then we have chances to make some bigger progress. If you don't show yourself, of course nobody will know what a man you are, even if you are most clever, loyal and so on, also nobody else could know you, nor feel good about you.So after we have got a job, we can say we really get in the social life, at that time we will feel how important to have a good way to deal with the social life.
 I'm very silent, I know it's not good for me to adapt to the society so I must take some action in order to make myself better. I won't stop my steps to success. BATTLE MY WAY TO THE SOCIAL LIFE.
 If the social life is like the sea, our individual life is just a pond of water, so how can we just want a pond of water and never think about to have fun in the sea?
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
